I ain't worried 'bout nothin',
I ain't wearin' na-nada
I'm sittin' pretty, impatient,
but I know you gotta
Put in them hours, I'mma make it harder
I'm sending pic after picture,
I'mma get you fired
I know you're always on the night shift
But I can't stand these nights alone
And I don't need no explanation
Cause baby, you're the boss at home
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
But you gotta put in work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
Let my body do the work, work,
work, work
Work, work, work
We can work from home, oh, oh, oh-oh
Let's put it into motion,
I'mma give you a promotion
I'll make it feel like a
vacay, turn the bed into an
ocean
We don't need nobody, I just
need your body
Nothin' but sheets in between
us, ain't no getting off early
And I know you're always on
the night shift
But I can't stand these nights alone
And I don't need no explanation
Cause baby, you're the boss at home
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
But you gotta put in work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
Let my body do the work, work,
work, work
Work, work, work
We can work from home, oh, oh, oh-oh
Oh yeah, girl go to work for
me (Work for me)
Can you make it clap, no hands for me?
Take it to the ground, pick it up for me
Look back at it all over me (Oh yeah)
Put in work like my timesheet
She ride it like a '63
I'mma buy her new Céline
Let her ride in a foreign with me
Oh, she the bae, I'm her boo
And she down to break the rules
Ride or die, she gon' go
I'm gon' jugg, she finessin'
I pipe her, she take that
Put in overtime on your body
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work (You ain't
gotta go to work, no oh oh)
But you gotta put in work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work (No....)
You don't gotta go to work,
work, work, work
Work, work, work
Let my body do the work, work,
work, work
Work, work, work (No, no, no,
no, no, no!)
We can work from home, oh, oh, oh-oh
Yeah, we can work from home
Yeah
www.RentAnAdviser.com